哇 怎么回事
Whoa. What's all this?
妈妈听到我们抱怨说好无聊
Mom heard us say we were bored.
衰了吧
Suckers.
她从外面都能听到
She heard us from outside.
她简直有顺风耳 就像导盲犬
She has super good hearing, like a seeing eye dog.
那些狗有过度发达的听力 以此来弥补
They have overdeveloped hearing to make up for the fact that--
等等 导盲犬本身没有瞎
Wait, the dogs aren't blind.
等等 好像是瞎的吧
Wait. Are they?
不对 这样说不通啊
No, that wouldn't make sense.
你说得对
You're right.
只要耐心等待 她自己就能琢磨出答案
If I wait long enough, she can get there by herself.
快猜 姑娘们
Quick, girls--
《月满抱佳人》中著名的丹尼
Famous Danny from "Moonstruck."
艾啰
Aiello?
[丹尼·艾洛 电影演员]
[Danny Aiello]
菲尔 幸好找到你了
Hey, Phil. I'm glad I caught ya.
什么事
What's up?
是关于斯蒂芬和斯特凡的
Uh, it's about Steven and Stefan.
他们想再看一次布洛尔街上的房子
They wanna see that house on Briar again.
真的吗 我都带他们去看过5次了
Really? I showed it to them five times.
上次去看时 我以为他们总算看对眼了呢
Last time we were there, I think they got mail.
所以我才给你打电话啊
Yeah, well, that's why I'm calling.
他们不喜欢去烦别人 只喜欢烦我
They hate upsetting people, unless, of course, it's me.
所以他们才不介意清晨7点就把我闹醒
Then they don't mind waking me up at 7:00 A.M.,
要我给你打电话
asking me to call you.
没问题 反正我也没事
It's no problem. I'm just hanging around.
正好有点闲得无聊
Kind of bored, really.
怎么了
What?
我们今天的日行一善完成了
Well, we did our good deed for the day.
没错 为了我们的死对头 他们有完没完啊
Yeah, for the enemy. Don't they have enough?
我们从一年前就计划领养一个儿子
It's been about a year since we decided to adopt a boy.
同时 我们的朋友斯蒂芬和斯特凡
Meanwhile, our friends Steven and Stefan
也决定要一个孩子
decided that they wanted a baby, too.
好奇他们这念头从哪里偷来的啊
Wonder where they got that idea?
我们还在等待之中 他们却已经
Well, we're still waiting, but they already got their kid
通过代孕生下了孩子
because they went through a surrogate.
他们对此叽叽喳喳个没完
Which is all they talk about.
你要一直这么说话吗
Are you gonna keep doing that?
没准哦
I might.
我得带人去看房子了
I have to go show a house.
不过首先 艾尔顿·约翰在70年代时的性向是
But first, what was Elton John's sexual orientation in the '70s?
拜[音同Bi 双性恋]
Bye.
-你已经说过一次了 -经典永流传
- You've done that one before. - And it never gets old,
就像奇异船长本人一样
like the good Captain Fantastic himself.
克莱尔 你知道吗
Hey, Claire, guess what?
抱歉 亲爱的 我没空说话
I'm sorry, honey, I can't talk right now.
我答应了送贝瑟妮去机场
I told Bethenny I would take her to the airport.
我迟到了 她会赶不上飞机的 钥匙呢
I'm late, and she's gonna miss her flight. Where are my keys?
这椅子怎么还在这 我以为你和卢克
Why is that chair still here? I thought you and Luke
已经把它搬去路边了呢
were gonna put it out on the sidewalk.
你没空说话 却有空要我做家务
So you can't talk unless it's about my chores?
你何不现在把活干好 也免得你这么无聊
Why don't you just do it now, and you won't be so bored?
你刚才听见了
You heard that?
什么都逃不过我耳朵
I hear everything.
是找我的
That's for me.
利昂 小平头真清爽
Hey, Leon. Nice buzz cut.
对某些人来说 洗发水根本没用
Yeah, for some people, the shampoo doesn't work.
只会让头虱越发猖狂
It only makes the lice angry.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
天呐 怎么会这样
Oh, no. No--oh, God.
艾丽克斯 站着别动
Um, Alex, do not move.
海莉 立刻打扫干净 听见了吗
Haley, clean this up, okay?
谁会在花瓶里装满弹子球啊
Who fills a vase with marbles?
谁会看不见一个装满弹子球的花瓶呢
Who doesn't see a vase filled with marbles?
谁想聆听一大叠盘子被打破的乐曲
Who wants to hear a bunch of plates crashing?
菲尔 亲爱的 快来厨房帮帮姑娘们
Phil! Honey, the girls need you in the kitchen!
谢谢你的帽子 利昂 戴着有点痒呢
Thanks for the hat, Leon. It kind of tickles.
菲尔
Phil!
把它救活需要多少电啊
How much electricity do we need to bring this back?
用不着那么高深的知识
It's not rocket science.
我们只是要让只死松鼠复活而已
We're only reanimating a squirrel.
菲尔 事态紧急
Phil! Now!
听起来不错嘛 不 等一下
Sounds great. No, hang on.
歌洛莉亚 曼尼呢
Gloria, where's Manny?
几个邻居小孩邀请他一起去踢橄榄球
Some neighborhood kids have invited him to play football.
他说他去进行晨间散步保健了
He said he was taking his morning constitutional.
他在摆弄他的卡丁车 不过他会去的
He's working on his go-cart, but he'll be there.
好 到时候见
Okay. See you then.
曼尼没法去和他们踢球了
No, Manny cannot go and play with those boys.
玛戈正在帮我们搞下午去剧院的票
Margo is trying to get us theater tickets for this afternoon.
歌洛莉亚 你和曼尼黏得够紧了
Gloria, you and Manny do enough together.
我们让他自己决定吧 他去哪里散步了
Let's let him decide. Where's he walking?
不知道 不过就他哼的歌来看
I don't know. But according to the song he was singing,
大概是在街道的向阳处散步呢
he was going to the sunny side of the street.
再多的话也不足以说明 那孩子多么需要踢橄榄球
I cannot express to you enough how bad this kid needs football.
妈 快看我找到了什么
Mom! Look what I found!
第99个硬币
Number 99!
在曼尼5岁时 我们家境贫穷
When Manny was 5, we didn't have much.
无依无靠
We were on our own.
所以我们总是幻想能中个彩票
So we always dreamed of winning the lottery.
我们想如果收集起100个人像朝上的幸运分币
We figured if we collected 100 lucky heads-up pennies
再用它买张彩票 铁定能中
and bought a ticket with them, we couldn't lose.
但现在我找到了好老公
But now I have a wonderful husband,
有了好归宿
a beautiful home...
我觉得自己已经中大奖了
I feel like I already won the lottery.
所以万一中奖 能全部归我吗
So I can keep whatever we win?
想得美 大部分硬币都是我捡的
I think no. I found most of them.
能把这个放到存钱罐里吗
Can you put this in the jar with the others?
没问题
Si.
啊 我忘了
Ay. I forgot.
你保险箱的密码是什么来着
What is the combination to your safe?
我还是跟你一起去吧
I'll just come with you.
噢 真有意思 难道我们家的情况是
Oh, yes, 'cause that's how this arrangement works--
靠你们俩来养活我吗
I take money from you!
你好
Hello?
玛戈啊 不 她刚上楼去了
Oh, hi, Margo. No, she just ran upstairs.
听着 那些剧院的票啊
Listen, about these theater tickets--
你不用费那么大劲去
Don't knock yourself out trying to...
已经搞到了
Oh, you did?
那个 抱歉现在才通知你
Well, sorry to do this last minute,
可他们去不了了
but they can't go.
不 曼尼有个橄榄球比赛 所以
No, Manny has a football game, so...
杰 能帮我把茶泡上吗
Jay, could you steep my tea?
再多的话也不足以说明 那孩子多么需要踢橄榄球
I cannot express to you enough how much this kid needs football.
整幢房子的参观结束
And that is the whole house...
再一次的
Again.
我喜欢这房子 可不是那种喜欢
I love it, but I just don't love it.
你喜欢吗
Do you love it?
当然 我当然喜欢
I love it. I absolutely love it.
我就是不太确定是不是爱上它了
I'm just not sure if I'm in love with it.
我懂的
Oh, yeah.
我们公司有个说法
We have an expression around the office
把那些做不成的买卖叫做
for when a sale just isn't happening--
佣金无望
"Commission: Impossible."
那是对他们来说
Maybe for some people.
我忘了之前有没有提过
Not sure if I mentioned it before,
这房子可是附带有
but the house does come with a hookup
一台欧式洗衣机的
for a European washing machine.
这个我喜欢
Oh, I love that.
真抱歉
Oh, so sorry.
"老大"来电
It's the boss.
嗨 我在回家路上呢
Hi. I'm on my way home.
刚给海莉打电话 一直没人接
I've been calling Haley, but nobody's answering.
都还好吧
Is everything okay there?
一切都好
Everything here is great.
那太好了 你把椅子搬出去了没
Oh, thank god. Did you put the chair out front?
还没呢
Not yet.
亲爱的 一会赶不上垃圾车收垃圾了
Honey, you're gonna miss the trash pickup.
别担心 就算他们不要 别人也会要的
Don't worry. If they don't take it, someone else will.
谁没事会从我们草坪上
Who is gonna pick up
把那破椅子搬走啊
that ratty chair off our lawn?
开什么玩笑 它好着呢
Are you kidding? It's in great shape.
超级舒服 人见人爱花见花开
Super cozy. People are always commenting on it.
相信我 今晚前就会有人要的
Trust me, it'll be gone by the end of the day.
拜托 现在就扔掉
Please, just do it now.
我没办法
I can't.
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
等我这儿客户走了
when I'm done with these clients,
我会给卢克和利昂打电话
I'll call Luke and Leon.
我肯定会说服他们的
I know I can talk them into it.
我们可不能把这房子让给卢克和利昂
We are not losing this house to Luke and Leon.
你说给他俩打电话是什么意思
What do you mean, "Call luke and leon"?
你不在家的吗
Aren't you at home?
不在 你走之前我就走了
No, I left right before you did.
菲尔 我们家 那些娃
Phil, the house... The--the kids...
天呐 那松鼠
Oh, god, the squirrel.
喂
Hello?
我们要了
We'll take it.
佣金
Commission...
到手
Accomplished.
你现在的生活多美好啊
So how great is your life right now, huh?
新房子 新宝宝
A new house, a new baby,
斯特凡的止秃药也开始起效了
Stefan's propecia's kicking in.
是他的短信 他在路上了
That's him. He's on his way.
他短信里写的"路上"
He texted "O.M.W."
我们带着孩子开车的时候
We try to keep our texts short
总是尽量保持短信简洁
when we're driving with the baby.
哇噻 你俩真是好家长
Oh, well, what wonderful parents you are.
你们一定有点嫉恨我们吧
You guys hate us a little bit, don't you?
-没 哪会啊 -有那么点
- No. God, no. - Just a little.
你们考虑过代孕吗
Have you thought about surrogacy?
自己造个婴儿
At least you'd be making a baby
至少要比等着哪个孕妇
instead of waiting around for some pregnant mom
来选你们要好些
to maybe pick you.
我们倒是考虑过
Well, we considered it,
可是我们不知道怎么决定谁来... 莉莉呢
But how do you decide which one will--where's Lily?
-睡觉呢 -给"蛋糕"上"糖霜"[受孕]
- Sleeping. - Ice the cupcake.
这有什么不能在莉莉面前说的
That you couldn't say in front of Lily?
听到这话她就会想要吃蛋糕
Well, then, she'd want a cupcake. Yeah, well...
混捐的好处就在这
But that's the beauty of the swirl.
混捐
The swirl?
夫夫二人同时捐精 然后混在一起
You both donate, they mix it up,
让卵细胞受精
Fertilize the egg.
谁都不知道亲爹是谁
You never know who the father is.
斯特凡来了
Ooh. That's Stefan.
我们是不是该考虑下混捐
Yeah, maybe we should think about this swirl.
那个 我觉得代孕不适合我俩
Well, I-I didn't think surrogacy was for us.
总有一个人 会有种被排挤在外的感觉
But, you know, 'cause one of us would feel left out.
可是如果不知道谁是亲爹的话
Yeah, but if you don't know whose it is...
抱歉我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
同志们 来认识一下罗可
Guys, meet Roco.
罗可还是可可啊[茶色]
Roco or Cocoa?
看他在球场上
Look at him out there.
太刺激了
Oh, ay. This is so exciting.
加油冲啊 漂亮
Go ahead! Attaboy!
-冲啊 往前冲 -跑啊曼尼 跑啊
- Go! Go ahead! Attaboy! - Go, Manny! Run!
我知道歌洛莉亚会发现我向她撒谎了
I knew Gloria would find out I lied about those tickets.
可是我觉得 等她看见曼尼在球场上
But I figured when she saw Manny out there,
跟其他孩子开开心心地玩
playing with all those other kids,
她会感谢我的
she'd thank me.
那是我想象中的美事
That's what I figured.
快跑 快跑
Go! Go!
他干嘛呢这是
What the hell's he doing?
跑啊曼尼 跑啊
Run, Manny! Run!
妈妈 第100个硬币
Mom! Number 100!
我们现在运气足够了
Now we have the lucky--oh!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
没人死掉
Nobody's dead.
也可能 我们都死了
Or... We're all dead.
损失了多少盘子
How many plates did we lose?
一个都没坏 卢克和海莉用饼干烤盘
None. Luke and Haley used cookie sheets
在一地玻璃弹中给我清理了一条路出来
to clear a path through the marbles for me.
玻璃弹呢
Where are the marbles?
在这呢
Right here.
海莉
Oh, Haley!
我在里面灌了胶水 以后不会再倒出来了
I put glue on them so it doesn't happen again.
椅子呢
What about the chair?
利昂和我用滑板把它推到外边去了
Leon and I rolled it outside on some skateboards.
松鼠呢
The squirrel?
你觉得我会允许那种荒唐事发生吗
You think I was going to let that happen?
那些孩子离开父母也会活得好好的
These kids are going to survive.
他们集我和菲尔的优点于一身
They are the best of me and Phil.
卢克利用了滑板 海莉把弹珠全粘起来
Luke using the skateboards, Haley gluing the marbles--
完全遗传了菲尔
That is pure Phil.
艾丽克斯让一切保持井然有序
Alex keeping everyone in line--
完全遗传了我
Pure me.
有时候我真担心会没人喜欢艾丽克斯
Sometimes I worry no one's gonna like Alex.
好了 小老弟
There you go, buddy.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么了 需要什么东西 我给你拿
What? You need anything? I'll get it.
牛排酱 不过没关系
Steak sauce, but it's okay.
我活动活动可能更好
It's probably good for me to move around.
杰 看见你这么照顾他可真温馨
Oh, Jay, it's so nice to see you take care of him like that.
这有什么好惊讶的 他是我们儿子
Why are you surprised? He's our kid.
我们家的人就是要互相照顾
We take care of each other in this family.
我想灭了你
I want to kill you.
让我猜猜 玛戈告的密
Wild guess--Margo?
听我解释
Let me explain.
你别找借口
There is no excuse.
父母间的私人恩怨 我还是回避为好
This is something private. I'm gonna get outta here.
所以你才表现得那么好
So that's why you were being so nice.
你骗我的朋友
You lied to my friend...
你让曼尼去踢橄榄球
you made Manny play the american football...
他被人撞成这样都是你害的
it is your fault that he got estamped.
该说是你的错吧
Or is it your fault?
他停下来去捡一枚硬币 真让人大跌眼镜
He stopped to pick up a penny, for god sake.
小心说话 杰
Be careful what you say, Jay.
你现在的状态岌岌可危
You're skating on thin eggshells right now.
我只是想让他走出家门
I tried to get him out there
和他同龄人一起玩
With kids his own age...
他这个年纪就该如此
Which is what he should be doing...
而不是一下午都陪在他妈咪身旁
And not spending another afternoon with his mommy.
你要是对曼尼的教育方法有意见
If you have a problem with the way manny's being raised,
你就跟我明说
You talk to me!
-我不正在说嘛 -我不想听
- I am. - I don't wanna hear it!
菲尔 你真的用不着这样
Phil, you really didn't have to do this.
我今天能卖掉那房子多亏了你们
I sold a house today because of you two.
请你们吃顿饭是最起码的了
The least I can do is buy you dinner.
我看过那房子 漂亮极了
I saw that house. It is gorgeous.
-我知道 -我们真为他们高兴
- I know. - We're real happy for them.
他们给我看了他们家孩子的照片
They showed me a picture of the baby.
那小家伙多萌啊
How adorable is that little guy?
是的 我们真为他们高兴
Yes, we're real happy for them.
行了 你该悠着点喝了
Okay, you might wanna slow down there.
怎么了 我在玩一种新型酒桌游戏
What? I'm playing a new drinking game.
叫做 "郁闷在心头 美酒喝进口"
It's called "Every time I'm depressed, I take a drink."
还真有那种游戏
That game exists.
叫做酗酒
It's called alcoholism.
抱歉 你说得对
Oh, I'm sorry, you're right. I'm...
我在自我沉沦 那一点都不好
I'm wallowing, and it's not cute.
敬高兴点的事
To happier things.
没错 敬高兴点的事
Yes. To happier things.
-高兴点的事 -对 -举杯
- Happier things, - Yes. - There you go.
我还记得喝前几杯时的事
I remember the first few drinks...
但是后来嘛 就只有支离破碎的记忆了
And, um, after that, the night's just bits and pieces.
我要干一件我以前从没干过的事
I wanna do something I never do--
显摆我家的孩子们
Brag about my kids.
今天 他们又聪明
Today, they were resourceful,
又有责任感 他们
They were responsible, they...
降价四成
Put 40% down.
带他们看5次房其实也是值得的
It was worth showing the house five times
等待着...
And waiting...
一年的等待
Almost a year.
开什么玩笑 谁他妈要...
Seriously! Who do you have to...
吹 那真的挺烫的
Blow. That's really hot.
你为什么不把它凉一凉 尝点这个
Why don't you let it cool down? Try some of the...
墨西哥裔
Mexican!
那孩子明显是墨西哥种
The baby is clearly mexican!
所以 混捐不行 完全是自欺欺人
So, you know, the swirl is out.
那简直让人想...
Ugh. It's enough to make you lose...
我想想
Track.
这是我第4杯吗
Is this my fourth drink?
是我第4杯
It's my fourth.
我是不是说了两遍第4杯
I said "Four" Twice, didn't I?
我说了 是不是
I did, didn't I?
我想我们得需要四辆出租
I think we're gonna need four cabs...
-两辆 - 两辆 都是你害我的
- Two! - Two! You made me!
我 我貌似记得 有人还哭了
I-I vaguely remember... Someone crying?
如果我们找代孕妈妈
If we ever did surrogacy,
我想让你来捐精
I would want you to be the donor.
你那么聪明 还那么帅
You're so smart, you're so handsome.
别说了 应该是你捐啦
Oh, stop it! It should be you!
-你那么风趣又有才华 -好了啦
- You're so fun! You're so talented! - Okay.
真不公平啊 我好爱你们夫夫啊
It's not fair. I love you both so much.
如果你们要小孩
If you could have a baby
如果他是你们俩的结合
that was a mix of the two of you,
我会非常爱那个宝宝的
I would love that baby so much.
你嘴真甜
That is so sweet.
-我是说真的 -你真好
- I meant it. - That is so sweet.
天啊 伙计们 我们可以这么干
Oh, my god. You guys, we could do this.
我们可以的
We could do this.
我们可以生一个
We could make a baby
融合塔克家和普里契特家血统的孩子
that is half Tucker and half Pritchett.
你说的和我想的是一个意思吗
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
是
Yeah.
克隆吗
Cloning?
不是 不是
No. No.
我是说
I'm saying...
我捐出卵子
I give the egg.
是的
Yeah.
我捐卵子 这不就有普里契特血统了吗
I give the egg. That's the Pritchett side.
然后小卡 你就捐出精子 对不
And then, Cam, you're the father, right?
然后 就 融合一下
And then we just, like, mix it
然后就把它放进代孕妈妈的肚子里
And put it in a, like, a surrogate lady thing,
然后砰 宝宝就有了
And then bang! We have a baby.
你是认真的吗
Oh. Are--are you serious?
你愿意那么做吗
You would do that?
我会甚感荣幸的
I would be honored.
二位 如果说我今天学到了什么的话
You guys, you guys, if there's one thing I have learned today,
那就是看着你们的宝宝
It's the pleasure of looking at your children,
然后从他身上看见你们俩的影子
And seeing both-- both of you in there.
而且我愿意让你们经历这种事情
And I want you to have that experience.
是的 我们期盼已久
Yeah. We want that.
还有更好的呢
And something else...
伙计们 我生的娃超棒的
guys, I make really good babies.
-是 -我好像有什么魔法卵子什么的
- Yes. - I have, like, magic eggs or something.
-是 -真是金牌卵子啊
- Yes! - They're golden.
天啊 菲尔啊
Oh, gosh. Oh, Phil,
我真 我真不知道该说什么好了
I don't--what do-- what do you say about this?
我觉得孩子将会是我们大家的
I think we're all having a baby!
来个桌抱
Aah! Table hug!
亲娘的七舅老爷啊
Sweet potato fries!
-我都干了什么啊 -我知道
- What have I done? - I know.
我当时想什么呢啊
What was I thinking?
我 我 我喝醉了然后就要生个娃了
I-I-I just get drunk and I bring a baby into the world?
那你就会生第4个孩子 我们4个人的孩子
That would be 4 for 4.
我绝对不能那样
I can't go through with it.
别慌 你还啥都没捐呢
Don't panic. You haven't donated anything yet.
况且 你的卵子还有活力吗
Besides, what are the chances your eggs even work?
或者我们干脆不承认说过那些
What are the chances we can pretend I never said that?
那太诡异了 那是我弟弟啊
It's weird. It's my brother.
然后就会有一个小孩出生
And then there would be this baby over there
是我的卵子发育的 却又不是我生出来的
That's my baby, but it's not my baby...
听着不错 你就这么说就行
That actually sounds good. Just say that.
再过两小时 我们去你爸家吃早午餐就会看见他了
We're gonna see him for brunch in two hours over at your dad's
那好像有点 太早[快]了吧
Ooh. That seems... Soon
而且很难面对
And--and hard.
如果我拿你当挡箭牌怎么样
What if... What if I blame it on you?
如果我说是你不同意行不
What if we say that you're not okay with it?
-不行 -为什么
- No! - Why?
你真不介意另一个男人给你妻子的卵子受精吗
Are you really okay with another man fertilizing your wife's egg?
-当然介意 听着都恶心 -就是
- Of course not! That's creepy. - Yes.
况且 万一你和小卡生出了更优质的孩子
Plus, what if you and Cam make a better baby than we did?
不会发生的 菲尔说了"不"
It's settled. Phil says "No."
你以为他们会相信 你顺从了我的否决吗
Like they're really gonna believe that I overruled you?
-也是 -对吧
- Right. - Come on.
他们会心碎的
They're gonna be crushed.
他们盼个孩子盼了好久
They've waited so long for this baby.
也许他们现在也想反悔了呢
Maybe they're having second thoughts, too.
看看 这是我和克莱尔的宝宝的样子
Look--this is what my baby with Claire would look like.
这是什么玩意儿
What is this? What...
我找到一个网站 父母可以上传自己的照片
Okay, well, I found a web site where couples can upload pictures...
然后它能合成宝宝的照片
and then it shows them what their baby would look like.
这是歌洛莉亚和我的孩子
This is... Gloria and I.
无法抗拒吧
Couldn't resist.
天呐 简直是曼尼的翻版嘛
Wow. That-- that looks exactly like Manny.
简直是像得诡异
Like--like weirdly so.
另一张是什么
What--what's this other picture?
别吃醋
Don't be jealous.
这张
But this...
是我和贾斯汀·汀布莱克的孩子
is me and Justin Timberlake.
小卡 我们有个问题
Cam, we have a problem.
怎么了 你能天天念叨瑞恩·高斯林
Oh, what? You can talk about Ryan Gosling all day,
-而我刚说一两句 -不不不
- but the moment I say something-- - No, no, no,
关于这个孩子 我
About this baby. I...
我觉得我不能接受这样做
I don't think I can do it.
什么 为什么 这样很棒
What--why? Why--it's perfect!
我们能有个同时拥有我们两个人基因的孩子
It's our chance to have a baby that's part me, part you!
不不 是你和克莱尔的基因
No, no! It's part you and part Claire.
没我的份儿
I'm nowhere in there.
而且我不能忽略的事实是
And it's not like I can pretend.
她不是什么陌生的卵子捐赠者
It's--she's not some egg donor that we don't know.
她是克莱尔
It's Claire.
我们抬头不见低头见的
You know, we see her all the time.
我们以后要怎么告诉那个孩子
And what are we supposed to tell the baby?
向你的姑"妈"问好
"Say hi to your aunt mommy!"
-多可爱 -不 一点儿也不可爱
- Adorable. - No, not adorable.
绝对不行
Appalachian.
对不起 小卡
Okay, I'm--I'm sorry, Cam.
杰说我太黏着曼尼了
Jay says that I'm smothering Manny...
但我只是太喜欢他了
But I'm just enjoying him.
我是说 他们还能孩子多久呢
I mean, they're only gonna be boys for a short time.
这房子里最棒的经历
Best time ever in this house!
菲尔 我不太喜欢这样
I'm uncomfortable with this, Phil.
使用手册上特意指出"禁止推拉"
The manual specifically says "No towing."
这个世界上有两种人
There are two types of people in this world--
一种喜欢遵循使用手册
people who follow the manual,
另一种则喜欢亲自动手操作
and people who stick it to the manual.
你 被"伤"了
You... are hurt.
曼尼 发生什么了
Manny, what happened?
橄榄球伤
Football injury.
我妈会嚷嚷着告诉你的
My mom will yell you all about it.
你好 莉莉
Hola, Lily!
我亲爱的小公主想吃小饼干吗
Does my little princess want a cookie?
就一小块吧
Oh, well, you know, maybe just one.
她今天糖分摄入已经达到上限了
She's already had her sugar limit for today.
你怎么知道
How can you tell?
好吧 莉莉
Okay, Lily.
嘿 小两口
Hey, you two.
孩子们都到哪儿去了
So where-- oh, where are the kids?
海莉一会儿载他们来
Oh, Haley's driving them over separately.
大姑娘了哟
Oh! Big girl now.
-挺好的 -是
- That's great. - Yeah
昨晚真开心
So that was... so fun last night.
-相当开心 -是的 昨晚很愉快
- So fun. - Yeah, we had a great night.
是的
Yes.
我们要
We should--
别说
Jinx!
我们要走这边
Yeah, we're going this way, so...
等会儿见
We'll see you in a bit.
我没法开口
I cannot tell them.
我不能伤他们的心
I cannot break their hearts.
就因为怕尴尬 你要和小卡生孩子吗
So you're gonna have Cam's baby just to keep things from being weird?
怎么回事
Um, what?
你和小卡舅夫要生个孩子吗
You and Uncle Cam are having a baby?
孩子们 小声点
Kids, shh.
我们是讨论过关于
There was a discussion about the possibility
让你妈妈捐赠卵子
of your mom donating an egg
让他们能有自己的孩子这件事
so that the guys could have a baby.
但是我们觉得这不是一个好主意
But we decided it was not a good idea.
为什么 因为莉莉是个小怪胎吗
Why? Because Lily's such a mess?
有很多原因
For a lot of reasons.
-他们有 -但我们都同意她是个小祸害吧
- They have-- - But we can agree that she's a disastrous human being?
我觉得这主意不错
I think it's a great idea.
对 是个贴心的礼物 妈妈 很有创意
Yeah. It's a really beautiful offer, mom. I'm impressed.
天呐 小卡 他们已经告诉孩子们了
Oh, my god. Cam, they told the kids already,
他们看上去很期待
And they seem to be totally into it.
好吧 难道只有我吗
All right, is it just me?
只有我一个人觉得怪怪的吗
Am I the only one that thinks this is weird?
或许一点都不怪
Maybe it's not weird.
说不定我们是勇敢的先锋呢
Maybe we're pioneers.
不 我们才不是勇敢的先锋
No, we're hardly pioneers.
你有三个不同的吹风机 以备不同的天气下使用
You have three different hair dryers for different types of weather.
也许你需要一些时间来接受那个想法
Maybe it's just gonna take some time to get used to the idea.
-什么想法 -没什么
- What idea? - Oh. No.
杰
Um, well, Jay...
-小卡 -克莱尔已经
- Cam. - Claire has--
不 我 我觉得
No. I-I-I just don't think
我爸还没准备好接受那个设想 所以
my dad's really ready for this conversation. So...
别总觉得我是个老顽固 我已经进步了
Oh, stop acting like I'm some stodgy old coot. I've grown.
好吧
Okay.
杰 克莱尔同意捐赠她的卵子给我们
Um, Jay, Claire has, um, offered to give us one of her eggs
这样我们将会有个
so we can have a baby
一半普里契特一半塔克血统的孩子
that's half Pritchett, half Tucker.
那简直是违背自然规律 我反对
That's unnatural. I'm against it.
大事件 大事件 杰提出反对意见了
Oh, surprise, surprise. Jay is against something.
小卡和克莱尔想生个孩子
Cam and Claire wanna have a baby together.
你们不能那样做
You're not gonna do that.
那不该由你来做决定 爸爸
It's not your decision, dad.
你根本就是欠考虑
You're not thinking straight.
根本不该由你说了算 克莱尔和我是成年人
And you're not in charge. Okay, Claire and I are adults.
如果我们都同意这么做 这事就算定了
If--if we want this to happen, it--it's gonna happen.
看来想反悔也迟了
So much for second thoughts.
小姑娘 我要和你谈谈
Young lady, I need to have a talk with you.
-算了吧 -不行
- I don't... - No.
你没权利对别人的生活指手画脚
You don't get to tell everyone how to live their lives,
什么小男生不能和妈咪一起玩
that boys cannot spend time with their mommies
姐姐和弟夫不能生孩子
or that brothers and sisters can't make babies.
-你同意他们瞎胡闹吗 -不
- So you're all for this? - No.
那有违天理伦常 可那是他们的事
It's a freak show, but it's their freak show.
往事又重演了吗
So this is happening again?
我才不会因为我爸觉得
Well, I'm not gonna not do it
不该做 我就不去做
'cause my dad thinks I shouldn't.
我不太明白
You know, I'm not following.
就算真不做 那也得是我不想做
We're not doing it 'cause I don't want to do it.
我们不去做
What we're not doing
不能因为他不让我们做 我们才不做
is not doing it 'cause he doesn't want us to do it.
要不要孩子一句话吧
Just say baby or no baby.
是不是嫌我们这家人还不够亲密
Isn't it enough this family spends a lot of time together?
现在还得搞个近亲繁殖
Now we have to inbreed.
爸 这并不是近亲繁殖 而是...
Okay, dad, it's not technically inbreeding. It's, um...
我得说句 我觉得我妈这样做太勇敢了
For the record, I think what my mom is doing is very brave.
我喜欢这想法
I like it.
我一直想要个半弟弟半表弟什么的
I've always kind of wanted a half-brother, half-cousin.
真的吗 一直想要
Really? "Always"?
如果你好好想想
Well, I mean, if you think about it...
我们上次桌下会晤是什么时候
When was the last time we talked under a table?
老爸和歌洛莉亚的婚宴上
Dad and Gloria's wedding reception.
对哦
Oh, yeah.
我爱你 你知道的
I love you. You know that...
但我做不到
but I can't do this.
我也一样做不到
No, no, neither can I!
-是吗 -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
说真的吗 你也不愿...天啊
Are you serious? You can't--oh, god.
真是松了口气 抱歉
I'm so relieved. I'm sorry.
我...
I-I-I...
真抱歉我把大家卷进一团乱麻里
I am so sorry I led us down this road.
克莱尔 不用抱歉
No, no. No, Claire, don't be. Don't be.
其实这想法既无私又周到 典型的你
It was--it was generous and thoughtful, just like you.
我真心希望自己的孩子有这些优点
How could I not want those qualities in my child?
抱抱
Oh, come here.
真的是要近亲繁殖了吗
So this is really happening?
如果是又怎样 爸
Ah. What if it is, dad?
就是 我们这是姐弟情深
Yeah. What if we love each other,
很感人的好吧
and this is a beautiful thing?
-这是我们的决定 不关你事 -就是
- Okay, it's our decision. It's not yours. - Yeah.
要不要孩子一句话
So baby? No baby?
不要
No.
你没事吧
You okay?
我很好
Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
我知道你心里不舒服
Mm, I know it's been hard on you.
不如我俩今晚出去吃顿大餐吧
Hey, what if we went out for a nice dinner tonight?
挺好 那我打电话叫临时保姆
Oh, that'd be fun. Should I call the sitter?
知道我今天心里的人选吗
Yeah. Oh, you know what I was thinking today?
卢克怎么样
What about Luke?
他俩可要好了
Oh, he's so good with her,
瞧见他望她的眼神没
the way he looks at her...
天呐 小卡
My god, Cam.
瞧 她在整理自己的东西
Oh, look, she's organizing her things.
看她穿的衣服
Look at how she's dressed.
虽然不是亲生 但却超像咱们
We didn't make her, but she sure is us.
莉莉宝贝 如果你把鞋子放在...
Hey, Lily, honey, it might make more sense with the shoes...
米奇尔
Mitchell.
她这样摆弄娃娃真有爱
I like what she did with the dolls--
想怎么玩儿怎么玩儿
Play as you will. Play as you will.
大枚的 记得吗
The big one, remember?
最早发现的之一
One of the first ones we found.
在街边的水沟里
It was at the bottom of the gutter in the street.
是啊
Ay, yes.
我们把香口胶黏在你的拐杖上捡到的
We put the gum at the bottom of your walking stick.
看这个 绿色的
Ay, look at this one-- the green one,
在我的计程车里捡到的
The one we found at the floor of my taxi.
-你的计程车 -正是
- Your taxi? - Yes.
在我的生活富足之前
Before I had somebody running my life for me,
我是个夜间计程车司机
I used to drive a taxi at night.
曼尼就睡在我旁边的座位上
Manny would sleep in the seat next to me.
有一次 我猛踩刹车
One time, I had to hit the brakes so hard
他一头栽了下来 发现了这枚硬币
that he fell into the floor and he found the penny.
很幸运吧
Pretty lucky, huh?
八年了 真不敢相信终于集齐了
Eight years. I can't believe we're finally done.
我也不敢相信
Me, either.
走吧 我们去买彩票
Come. Let's go get your lottery ticket.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
我想你犯了个错误
I think you made a mistake here.
我做错什么了
What did I do now?
我数过了 只有96枚硬币
I counted these, and you've only got 96 pennies.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
恐怕是的
Afraid so.
看来你得继续收集了
I guess you're gonna have to keep lookin'.
见鬼 我数过了
Dang it! I counted those.
你自己数数吧
See for yourself.
现在上传你的照片
And now we upload your picture.
有意思 有意思
This is fun. This is fun.
稍微等一下
And in just a few short moments,
拜神奇高科技所赐
thanks to the magic of technology...
我们就会知道咱俩的孩子长啥样
We'll know what our baby actually looks--
-不要 -怎么回事 这什么东西
- Oh! No! - What happened? What is that?
你是把谁的照片传反了吗
Did you put one of us in upside-down?
没有 这真是...
No! That's actually--
别让我再看到这个
Okay, I-I don't want to see this anymore.
快关掉
Ohh. Turn it off.
关不掉
Oh, it's not turning off.
快拿东西遮住 我的妈呀
Well, throw something over it! That--oh, god!
我们扮演上帝的角色私自造人 瞧瞧可怕的后果吧
Yeah, well, we played god, and look what we brought forth.
爸爸 你们在看什么
Daddies, what are you looking at?
可能没那么糟
Maybe it wasn't that bad.
可能是我们反应过激了
No, no, it's possible that we overreacted.
对 可能是我们期望过高
Yeah. Maybe our expectations were just a little bit too high.
那小家伙其实还有几分可爱
That little guy had some cute features. Huh?
当然了 我俩的结合 不可能太糟
Of course he did. It's us. It can't be that bad.
再瞄一眼
Let's just take--